

(562) 977-7322 jimmyhwang@nyu.edu los angeles | new york city www.jimmyhwang.me

EXPERTISE

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe InDesign

Adobe Photoshop

Figma

Git

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

ReactJS

WordPress

EDUCATION

New York University

Bachelor of Science

Integrated Digital Media

Sep 2016 - May 2020

LANGUAGES

English

Korean

INTERESTS

Basketball & NBA

Cooking & Food

Esports

Music Production

SUMMARY

I have two years of digital design experience in various organizations from non-profits to consulting firms. Key strengths include web design & development, graphic design, and UI/UX design. I have excellent leadership, organization, and communication skills, with special experience in taking initiative and providing progress in the face of ambiguity.

EXPERIENCE

COMMUNITY LITERATURE INITIATIVE | Volunteer Web Designer

Los Angeles, CA | November 2020 - present

- Propose comprehensive web development plans using Wix and WordPress for Publishing Class, World Stage Press, and Sims Library of Poetry
- Complete projects from conception to development including web UI/UX design, graphic design, and website management
- Integrate integral SEO techniques increasing site sessions by 118%
- Increase on average 3.5% in conversion rate by optimizing the UI & UX on product pages of the e-Commerce website

JANG SOO SUSHI BAR | Freelance Web Developer

Hawaiian Gardens, CA | April 2020 - June 2020

- Managed and solely developed the business's official website using ReactJS, including mobile compatibility which accounted for around 80% of impressions
- Increased the accessibility of the restaurant's details and its menu to consumers, with over 950 clicks and 7,000 impressions since June 2020
- Designed a simple UI that was easy to navigate through for a consumer base that mainly consisted of older generation Korean-Americans
- Integrated integral SEO techniques and buzz words to attract viewers to the site

MCW GLOBAL | Graphic Design Intern

New York, NY | November 2019 - January 2020

- Worked closely with executives from New York and Africa to collaborate on design ideas on a tight schedule
- Utilized multiple software applications like Photoshop to design marketing posts, promotional materials, email blasts, and graphic banners
- Edited photos, audio files, and videos for website and social media use

HARGREAVES JONES | Web Consultant

New York, NY | April 2018 - January 2019

- Maintained the company's website using WordPress including search engine optimization, caching, spam filtering, and website security
- Designed and produced Project pages, News pages, and the Ideas page
- Created promotional material for marketing and advertisement purposes including website banners and HTML email templates
- Organized the website's files by properly archiving all material in a shared drive